[
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-35",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-insert-position/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P001_Search_insert_position.java",
    "name": "Search insert position",
    "serialNum": 1,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-03",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-69",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/sqrtx/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P002_Find_square_root.java",
    "name": "Find square root",
    "serialNum": 2,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-03",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-278",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/first-bad-version/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P003_First_bad_version.java",
    "name": "First bad version",
    "serialNum": 3,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-04",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Interactive"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-374",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/guess-number-higher-or-lower/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P004_Guess_number_higher_or_lower.java",
    "name": "Guess number higher or lower",
    "serialNum": 4,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-04",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Interactive"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-367",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-perfect-square/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P005_Valid_perfect_square.java",
    "name": "Valid perfect square",
    "serialNum": 5,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-04",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-441",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/arranging-coins/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P006_Arranging_coins.java",
    "name": "Arranging coins",
    "serialNum": 6,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-04",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Binary Search", "Math"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-704",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-search/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P007_Binary_search.java",
    "name": "Binary search",
    "serialNum": 7,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-05",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1346",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-n-and-its-double-exist/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P008_Check_if_n_and_its_double_exist.java",
    "name": "Check if n and its double exist",
    "serialNum": 8,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-05",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Hash Table", "Sorting", "Two Pointers"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2529",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-count-of-positive-integer-and-negative-integer/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P009_Maximum_count_of_positive_and_negative_integer.java",
    "name": "Maximum count of positive integer and negative integer",
    "serialNum": 9,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-06",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Counting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-744",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-smallest-letter-greater-than-target/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P010_Find_smallest_letter_greater_than_target.java",
    "name": "Find smallest letter greater than target",
    "serialNum": 10,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-06",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1351",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-negative-numbers-in-a-sorted-matrix/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P011_Count_negative_numbers_in_a_sorted_matrix.java",
    "name": "Count negative numbers in a sorted matrix",
    "serialNum": 11,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-27",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Matrix"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1011",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/capacity-to-ship-packages-within-d-days/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P012_Capacity_to_ship_packages_within_D_days.java",
    "name": "Capacity to ship packages within D days",
    "serialNum": 12,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-28",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1385",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-distance-value-between-two-arrays/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P013_Find_the_distance_value_between_two_arrays.java",
    "name": "Find the distance value between two arrays",
    "serialNum": 13,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-29",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Sorting", "Two Pointers"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-888",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/fair-candy-swap/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P014_Fair_candy_swap.java",
    "name": "Fair candy swap",
    "serialNum": 14,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-30",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Hash Table", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-34",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-first-and-last-position-of-element-in-sorted-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P015_Find_first_and_last_position_of_element_in_sorted_array.java",
    "name": "Find first and last position of element in sorted array",
    "serialNum": 15,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-31",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-852",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/peak-index-in-a-mountain-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P016_Peak_index_in_a_mountain_array.java",
    "name": "Peak index in a mountain array",
    "serialNum": 16,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-01",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-162",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-peak-element/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P017_Find_peak_element.java",
    "name": "Find peak element",
    "serialNum": 17,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-02",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Hard",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1095",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-in-mountain-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P018_Find_in_mountain_array.java",
    "name": "Find in mountain array",
    "serialNum": 18,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-03",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Interactive"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-33",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/searching/leetcode/P019_Search_in_rotated_sorted_array.java",
    "name": "Search in rotated sorted array",
    "serialNum": 19,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-06-03",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search"]
  }
]